All right. Hey, Gerard. Welcome. First
of all, welcome to Las Vegas. There's
been a lot of talks uh throughout the
draft about regards to your knee. I just
wanted to check in and see how is your
knee feeling. And are do you anticipate
getting a second surgery as a lot of
reports suggest?
>> Uh yeah, I mean I feel good, but as far
as like another surgery and all that,
that would just be strictly based off
what the team wants me to do. So,
whatever the team's plan for me is is
what I'll be doing.
>> Yeah. Jamal, how difficult has it been
the last couple days, you know, knowing
that your talent uh is what it is and
probably justified a much higher draft
pick, but you know, things beyond your
control caused you to have to wait this
out.
>> Uh, I mean, it's definitely uh Oh, wait.
Can you ask again? Hold on, my bad.
Somebody had just Can you ask that
again?
>> Yeah, just just uh how difficult it was
just kind of dealing with the fact that,
you know, you you know, you probably
should have been picked a lot sooner,
but situations beyond your control
caused you to, you know, fall a little
bit down in the draft.
Yeah, I mean it's it's definitely
difficult.
I mean
a plan for me and uh I mean
what like I just work there. I just
>> um
>> y'all hear me?
>> Yeah. Yeah. J. Uh
>> yeah.
>> So did you go into this draft knowing
that this likely could happen? You have
to So did you prepare yourself mentally
that you might not go as high as you
wanted to? And if so, did that kind of
ease a little bit or or how or that
still difficult to deal with?
>> Um, I mean, I was prepared for whatever
happened. But I mean, I will be go a
little uh to go higher for sure cuz I
mean I had a good pro day. Ran some good
times and just did good things like
that. But I mean, I was prepared for
whatever happened. Uh cuz I mean it's
not in my control and I'm just like I'm
just truly blessed that the team took me
anyways cuz this is a achievement to get
here in the first place.
>> Jam obviously you wasn't necessarily
expecting to to slide this far. But in
terms of the team that drafted you and
the Raiders, did you have any previous
conversations with the Raiders
throughout the draft process or was them
picking you and you know hearing them
call your name, was that a surprise to
you?
Uh, I had a zoom with them the day
before the draft. Uh, so I mean they
kind of got on my radar a little bit. I
was kind of thinking like something was
up. Uh, but I mean I I didn't really
have a clue where I was going to go to
to be honest. So I mean just it's just a
blessing to get picked by the Raiders.
>> Jer, this is Hondo Carpenter. There's no
doubt about your talent. The tape just
tells the story. But there's another guy
connected to this franchise who was
picked in the sixth round and Tom Brady
that ended up being the greatest player
of all time. Can you use guys like him
as a motivation to go prove the rest of
the league wrong at being selected in
the fourth round with the talent you
have, sir?
>> Oh, yeah. I feel like all of just
motivation just fueling me. Uh like
Yeah. It's just fuel to be honest.
Hi, Jamro. Heidi Fang, Las Vegas Review
Journal. I'm just wondering like what
excites you the most right now about the
team that the Raiders have been putting
together through the draft and the
offseason, what you've seen.
>> Yeah, from what I've seen, I see a a
great uh I see a great team to be
honest. Uh I mean, I got some teammates,
old teammates on the team right now and
just they're kind of telling me what the
uh organization is like. So, just
knowing that I'm going to a great
organization just feels uh I feel good
going into it.
>> Hey, Dream. Uh Sam Warren from The
Athletic. You know, sitting out last
year with the torn ACL, was there
anything that you learned about yourself
as a player or anything going through
that process you think helped you going
into the NFL?
>> Yeah. Something I feel like I learned
about myself is just like I feel like
I'm super mentally strong. Uh I feel
like I've just been through a lot. I got
a a story that I'm still trying to still
telling. So, I mean, just
Yeah, that's that's what it is to be
honest.
>> Hey, Jam. Jesse Merrick with Silver
Black Sports Network. I understand your
first career pick was against Fernando
Mendoza. Just curious what you remember
about that moment and now the
opportunity to play with him here in
Vegas.
>> Yeah, I mean it was probably one of one
of the top moments in my life. My first
college pick. Uh we talked after that
game too. just uh chopped it up a little
bit. But I mean it was it was it was a
good good to know we going to be on the
same team too. Uh best quarterback like
in college football now going to be the
best in the league.
>> Sorry Jam going back just um on the knee
issue. What is your understanding of
where where it is healthwise and I guess
what were you telling teams about where
you believed you are? I know you said
you want you want the team to look at
it, but here's where where do you think
you are and what have you been told
about it?
>> Yeah, I mean all my doctors like that
did my surgery, they tell me they told
me I'm good. I feel like I'm good. But
um I mean but if the team if there's
something that they're want me wanting
me to do for the longevity of my career,
like I'm willing to do that, I'mma uh
listen to the team cuz I feel like they
have my best interest for me. So
honestly, just whatever the team's
playing for me is, I'mma do that.
Also, you kind of just uh previously
brought up kind of getting the vibe on
the team, the temperature from former
teammates, you know, what's your
relationship like with uh Dante
Thornton, you know, and what is it going
to be like to be able to test your
talents against him once again?
>> Yeah. Uh I mean, we got a good
relationship. if he just texted me uh
like we reunited again back in the same
locker room, get to uh just be cool with
each other again and all that. But uh I
mean getting to go against him again in
practice. I feel like me and Dante uh
the year like we would me and him we
would battle every day. So just getting
to we made each other way better. I feel
like throughout that season he's part of
the reason why I had the season I had
just guarding him every day making me
better. And then I feel like the same
with me uh him having to go against me,
I'm making him also better. So, I mean,
I think getting to do that again is just
going to improve both of our games.
>> The last one, Adam, go ahead.
>> I was just I was just wondering, were
you were you watching uh the draft as it
as it played out? Were you paying
attention to what was going on or was it
maybe too difficult as uh as the picks
kept coming off the board, you weren't
hearing your name? And um I guess what
was the call like when you finally got
it?
>> No, I was watching for sure. I mean, cuz
like this ain't something you could take
for granted. Like everybody this is
everyone's dream. So, like it's not
something you could just say, "I didn't
get drafted where I wanted, so I'm not
going to watch the draft no more." Like,
this is still a blessing uh to get
drafted. So, I mean, I was in there
watching it, got the call, super
excited, ready to get to work.
>> Awesome.
>> Thanks so much, man. Appreciate you.
Yeah,
>> appreciate y'all.